<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<document>
<webSite>http://www.321one.com/</webSite>
<webMaster>SAMHO Club</webMaster>
<updatePeri>60</updatePeri>
<item>
<title>
<![CDATA[看电影，搜资源神器。云盘精灵，只要是公开资源，且在百度网盘存储，几乎都能搜到。上网神器”油猴脚本]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://www.321one.com/1.html]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[看电影，搜资源神器，你懂的]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[
	www.yunpanjingling.com  云盘精灵，只要是公开资源，且在百度网盘存储，几乎都能搜到。虽然收费，但十分便宜，白菜价。http://clg8.org/
	磁力搜索引擎，可以搜索全网所有资源。
https://www.pianku.tv/  
免费在线看高清最新电影，最新的美剧、动漫、新电影...全都免费，还支持磁力下载，值得收藏。
上网神器”油猴脚本“，解除网页限制、自动网课答题、下载全网视频、自动下载图片、去水印视频下载...   你能想到的功能都有。
支持360、chrome、火狐 等主流浏览器，完全免费。网址：https://greasyfork.org/zh-CN/
]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[design,creat,设计,山合,picture,图片,art,艺术,blog,博客,pan,eBook,软件,电子书免费,PS,photoshop,pdf,好物分享,电影,美文]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[工具推荐]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[山合文化]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2020-12-16 10:29</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
	<title>
<![CDATA[[Windows] 老马家买的去头去尾版爱剪辑]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://www.321one.com/blog.html]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[看电影，搜资源神器，你懂的]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[
	爱剪辑应该挺多人用，平时剪剪小视频还是挺方便的，功能上虽然远不及adobe全家桶，但是修剪一些手机拍的小视频效率要比Pre高
	现在还不是选举日，但是数以千万计的美国人已经经历了排队等候投票的过程。即使对于那些有邮寄和投递选票选择的人，早期投票线在多个州已经延伸。

从理论上讲，提前投票意味着更少的人会试图在选举日参加投票——这是大流行期间的一件好事。但是，当提前投票本身导致大量人群——选民们只是不断来——我们想知道，我们是否真的避免了像我们所希望的那样多的病毒传播。
We’re less than three weeks away from Election Day, and although we’ve already seen an enormous uptick in the number of absentee ballots requested — more than a third of Americans plan to vote by mail because of the coronavirus — many people will still cast their votes in person. This means that people will assemble at polling places, as they did in the primaries held earlier this year and as they’re doing in states that have started early voting. This, of course, raises a difficult question: Could the simple act of voting worsen a public health disaster?
The billboards started popping up around Minneapolis in June. “Uptown reels after gunfire, bloodshed.” “Multiple shootings in metro area overnight.” Referencing quotes from local newspapers and TV stations, the signs were part of an ad campaign aimed at turning concerns over a spike in gun violence into a pro-police political movement.

]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[设计,咨询,报告,Design,远程工作,招聘,art,艺术,work,job,山合,商业合作,tool,工具]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[工具新闻]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[山合文化]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2020-12-16 10:29</pubDate>
</item>
</document>
